const blockchain_data = [
	{
		question: "What is a block in blockchain?",
		answer: "Data",
	},
	{
		question: "What is a node in blockchain?",
		answer: "Computer",
	},
	{
		question: "What is a hash function in blockchain?",
		answer: "Encryption",
	},
	{
		question: "What is consensus mechanism in blockchain?",
		answer: "Agreement",
	},
	// New questions
	{
		question: "What is the purpose of a Merkle tree in blockchain?",
		answer: "Efficiency",
	},
	{
		question: "What is a fork in blockchain?",
		answer: "Divergence",
	},
	{
		question: "What is the first block in a blockchain called?",
		answer: "Genesis",
	},
	{
		question: "What is the function of a timestamp in blockchain?",
		answer: "Chronology",
	},
	{
		question: "What is the basis of Proof of Stake in blockchain?",
		answer: "Stake",
	},
	{
		question:
			"What is a common security issue in blockchain related to spending the same digital currency twice?",
		answer: "Double-spend",
	},
];

export default blockchain_data;
